{
    "id": "346d7dc3c6b044f684ebc42ce3e334d2",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My sister and I enjoy ...................... in the sea.",
            "description": "After enjoy, we use an -ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to swim",
                "swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8475ab23f14b488fadff4187f6e15110"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think you have forgotten .......................... your homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to do",
                "doing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "12aa1aa394b54f77835a3c23a0358433"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works hard ....................... a living.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "earning",
                "to earn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8d73f13c48746debb77ae94608ccc90"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani studies .......................... good marks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "scoring",
                "to score"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbf05be728d54b628d504eb6e36dec4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler requested the passer-by ......................... him a hand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lending",
                "to lend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06c0d28cde314a518dcb574903ec96ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother did not let me ......................... out with my friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "going",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50b5dc92cd2a4df9a99ba4776eb7eaba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didnâ€™t let me ............................ his room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to enter",
                "enter",
                "entering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac2ab9c94cc4448bb4a7e8f18c25cd15"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children are busy .......................... their project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing",
                "do",
                "to do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efc23d175fc344e0bdf9fa6da4db0c52"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am looking forward ........................... you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seeing",
                "to seeing",
                "to see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a15f72beca5f4b40b99c1a0f49750a49"
        },
        {
            "question": "I meant ........................... the letter, but I forgot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to be posting",
                "to have posted",
                "posting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d47f1b3451a46b4b1b19574228f7f40"
        }
    ]
}